Get ready for a successful year — Save 40%  on Sender subscriptions! [Claim Now](https://auth.sender.net/register?scope=scope&client_id=21&response_type=code&redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fapp.sender.net%2F)

Get ready for a successful year — Save 40% on Sender subscriptions!

    Education

    Support

    Grow your business, not your expenses
    
    Turn curious visitors into devoted fans and drive more sales – no cost to get started!
    
    * Free Forever plan for 2,500 subscribers and up to 15,000 emails/month
    * Free & responsive email templates library
    * Free popups & forms

    * Intuitive drag-and-drop email builder
    * Unlimited automation and segmentation
    * Premade automation workflows

    No Credit Card Required. Cancel Anytime.

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy applies to www.sender.net , owned and operated by UAB Sender.lt. We realize that you care how your information is processed and shared, and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This document describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting our website at sender.net or using our service, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

General
-------

Sender is a company that provides digital marketing and ancillary services for its clients. Sender collects personal information about you during your use of our website and services and through our cookie technology as you use and navigate our website and service. Sender is the Data Processor, our customer is the Data Controller.

If you provide us with personal information (your name, postal address, telephone, or email address), or have done so in the past, via our websites, our publications or surveys, we may use that information to send you updates on our latest services and promotions or to contact you so that we may learn more about our customers.

You can choose to “opt out” of these communications. To state your contact preferences please contact us at [info@sender.net](mailto:info@sender.net) . To opt out of any email communications from us, please click the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the footer of the email in question.

We may use your data to collate and create an information database of visitors to our website in order to improve our website and our service and to provide relevant services and information to you. We may also share any aggregated information, but not individual data, with third parties which offer their goods or services on our websites to help them better understand our services and monitor their advertising reach on the sites.

Customer Data Processing
------------------------

Sender collects personal information from Customers who visit the Website and register with our Service. Sender is the data controller in regard to the Customer’s personal data. When the Customer registers with our Service, we require: username, password, email address, first and last name, country and billing information such as billing address, tax ID number. We may also ask Customers to provide additional personal information such as company name and other company and personal details that the Customer may opt out of by not entering data when asked. We use the Customers’ registration information to authenticate users and provide access to the Service. We also use the email addresses used in the registration information to communicate with our Customers. From time to time, Sender may contact you via email to notify you of changes to its Service, scheduled maintenance, information about Sender and promotional material from Sender. The Customer is obliged to update the data provided in the registration form as soon as any change in these data has occurred. We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you the Service. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Provision of personal data in connection with your use of the Service is voluntary. Note, however, that the refusal to provide certain data may make it impossible for you to use all or part of the Service functionalities.

Sharing Information Regarding the Customers and Subscribers
-----------------------------------------------------------

Sender will not share, sell, rent or trade the Customer’s and Subscriber’s personal information other than as disclosed within this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to disclose the Customer’s and Subscriber’s personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, Court order, or legal process served on Sender.

We use other third parties in a scope necessary to provide the Service, such as a credit card processing company to bill the Customer for services. When you sign up for the Service we will share your information as necessary for the third party to provide the Service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes.

If Sender is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

Website Use Information
-----------------------

Our servers automatically collect site use information, each time you visit the Website.

The Website use information includes, but is not limited to the following: domain names, operating system in use (e.g. macOS, Windows), browser (e.g. Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Internet Explorer) and version, the Website which referred you to us, and other similar information. This information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Website, pages viewed, time and date of visits, and other similar information. We may use and disclose site use information, for example, to measure the use of the Website, improve the content, explain the utility of the Website and services we provide, and to extend their functionality.

As is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track users’ movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

Similar to other commercial websites, “cookies” may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a small piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive, so we can recognize you when you return. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Our cookies collect general information that enhances our ability to serve you and measure the utility of the Website. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on the Website.

The use of cookies by third party web analytics partner is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. These third parties use session ID and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Website.

Information we collect may be used to enhance your use of the Website, and to provide you with the Service, arrange the Website in the most customer friendly way, communicate special offers and featured items, and/or respond to your questions and suggestions.

In the case of an agreement, personal information includes data that identifies you as the specific individual, i.e. your name, email address, phone number, geographical address, and/or company name and company address. This information is used to complete the account application process, Customer’s information request, and/or to verify the validity of the request, and to process payment.

We will use this information solely for processing payments for the Service that you ordered.

Sender collects only personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily registering to our Service. Sender shall advise you which information is mandatory to provide and what you do not have to fill in.

Information Security
--------------------

We believe that keeping personal information secure is one of our most significant responsibilities.

We restrict access to personal information about you to those employees and others who need to know that information to assist us in our business, or to provide services to you. We safeguard personal information, according to the established security standards and procedures, by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to the personal data information.

When we request Customers to enter sensitive information, such as credit card number, it is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry SSL and processed through a reputable payment processor. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon at the bottom of web browsers, e.g. Mozilla Firefox or Microsoft Internet Explorer, becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked or open, when you are just ‘surfing’.

All of our Customers’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are personally granted access to sensitive information.

Security
--------

Sender stores its servers in a highly secure server environment, with surveillance and support to prevent unauthorized access and data security.

We cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted over the Internet and through servers that are out of our control. We strive to protect your personal information but Sender cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to the Website or Services. Any data transmissions you make over the Internet are done so at your own risk. Once we receive the data transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security and privacy on our systems.

Customer Testimonials/Reviews
-----------------------------

We post customer testimonials/reviews on the Website which may contain personal information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial/review to post their name along with their testimonial/review. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please contact us at [support@sender.net](mailto:support@sender.net)

View, Change or Remove Information
----------------------------------

You may change or delete your profile information at any time by going to your profile page. Please contact us if you need assistance in updating or reviewing your information at [support@sender.net](mailto:support@sender.net).

Other Terms
-----------

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here prior to the changes taking effect.

If, however, we make material changes or Sender is going to use users’ personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via the Website prior to the change becoming effective. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the Website, or deleted their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.

Premium capabilities Feels enterprise,  
minus the price
--------------------------------------------------------

All the features your business needs to acquire high-quality leads, grow sales, and maximize revenue from campaigns  
using one simple dashboard.

Product

Resources

Support

Company

© 2012-2024 Sender.net
